Daniel Del Grosso

570-899-2071 / dannydelgrosso@gmail.com / https://danny-del.surge.sh / Philadelphia PA, 19128

A software developer with experience in producing clean and maintainable code for many large and small scale projects. Worked within many facets of software development including API design and Front End implementations.

Experience

Deacom Inc. Paoli, PA — Full Stack Software Engineer Feb 2019 - Present

I currently work on two different teams at Deacom. I am on the API team to help create 3rd party integrations into our main application such as TaxJar or FedEx. I also work on the frontend team to help maintain and enhance the UI and functionality of our eCommerce platform.

eNet Partners Inc. Montgomeryville, PA — Full Stack Software Engineer Oct 2016 - Feb 2019

Built and maintained the backend code on our ecommerce microsites for some of the most prominent names in the As Seen on TV industry. All sites were built with VB.net, Webforms, and MSSQL database.

Created Referral Management system inside a NopCommerce CMS.

Worked on internal applications for data aggregation.

IBM Rocket Center, WV — Application Developer July 2016 - Oct 2016

Built the backend functionality for internal project to help managers with signing and adding documents into job queues. Project was built in Angular 1, MongoDB, Express.js and Node.js.

United States Steel Pittsburgh, PA — Application Developer Intern May 2015 - July 2015

Designed and implemented an update to a Steel Coil Tracker Application which fixed issues with connection to internet while in warehouse and updating the Database. Built in VB.net and a SQL database.

Maintained internal websites.

Education

Indiana University of Pennsylvania - Indiana, PA
Bachelor's Degree of Science - Management Information Systems

Technology Stack

C#, MSSQL, .NET Framework React.JS, ES6, CSS, HTML, Node.JS